

**Personal info**Born in Terrassa on 03.02.1994

\* +34 601436012 +49 5770251085

★ Terrassa (Barcelona)

#### Languages

Catalan • • • • • • Spanish • • • • • • German • • • • •

#### **Programming Languages**

PHP	• • • • 0
Javascript:	• • • • 0
HTML / CSS	• • • • •
SQL	••••
Python	• • • • •
Kotlin	• • • • •
C++:	• • • • •

# Software tools, frameworks

Git	• • • • •
Linux	• • • • 0
Laravel	• • • • 0
Vue	• • • • 0
React	• • • • •
Postgres	• • • • •
Nodejs	• • • • •
Android studio	• • • • •
Latex	• • • • •
Daton	
Figma	••••
Figma Tableau	
e	• • • • •
Tableau	• • • • • •
Tableau Excel	

#### **Soft Skills**

- Logical mindset
- Hard working
- Empathic
- Open minded

# Interests

- Software development
- Science
- Language learning
- Hiking







# **Bernat Ferrer**

### Software engineer, PHP and Javascript

Fullstack web developer with a special interest in the final user experience of the product. Fronted development with vue and vuex, database managing, backend development with DDD and MVC, Unit testing, Restful and graphQL APIs and more.

#### **Professional experience**

## Fullstack developer at Meetaitech Barcelona. April 2021 - Now

Currently working at the Meetaitech startup. Here, we develop a pioneer product that tracks the online meetings in companies and handles the data produced . My duties here include taking part of the UI design, implementing it using Vue and the Vuex library, managing the Database and implementing solutions in the backend with PHP and Laravel.

### Fullstack developer at Assembler, Barcelona. June 2020 - Feb 2021

Working with the programming languages HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP, SQL and the frameworks Laravel, Nodejs and React.

One of the project consited in the development of a social network with PHP using the Laravel with the main features of a social network (comments, likes, following, notifications). Implementation of a relational database using SQL and database migrations. Usage of MVC pattern with object oriented programming. repo link

#### Android developer, Barcelona. March 2020 - June 2020

Development of an app for language learning using Kotlin and the MVVM pattern. Published on google play App link.

# Data analyst at M-net, Munich. Sept 2018 - Oct 2019

Analysis of revenue data using Tableau and Excel in order to optimize benefits and reduce loses.

# Physics Researcher at the USM, Munich. 2018 - 2019

Development of an interface for the visualization of data coming from astrophysical simulations of protoplanetary disks. Name of the master thesis: *Constraints in gap opening timescales in the HD 623296 protoplanetary disk*.

# **Education**

Master in software development Assembler School, Barcelona. 2020- Now

Astrophysics Master Ludwig Maximilians University, Munich (LMU). 2017-2019

Physics Degree Universitat Autónoma de Barcelona (UAB). 2012-2017

#### Additionally

A user experience course at LMU, Munich. 2019.

A six month internship at the European southern observatory (ESO), Munich. April -Sept 2018.

Volunteer in a homeless shelter in the city of Pittsburgh, USA. Summer 2013.

Private maths teacher for high-school students, Terrassa. 2012-2016.